<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-03-30T10:52:20+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Bang Bang Bunny</title><subtitle>Alba, Tha sinn a &apos;cumadh dhut!</subtitle><author><name>Nic The Geek</name></author><entry><title type="html">Bang Bang Bunny are sponsored by The Arts Council</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2023/02/04/BBBSponsoredByArtsCouncil.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Bang Bang Bunny are sponsored by The Arts Council" /><published>2023-02-04T03:45:13+00:00</published><updated>2023-02-04T03:45:13+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2023/02/04/BBBSponsoredByArtsCouncil</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2023/02/04/BBBSponsoredByArtsCouncil.html"><![CDATA[<p>Bang Bang Bunny are sponsored by The Arts Council England and were awarded the DYCP Grant in 2023 to fuse punk rap
    with Scottish Gaelic, to popularise an endangered language and history through music. Madaldn, born in Essex,
    descends from the Elliott Clan. She States “My grandad tells me how his grandad fought in Black Watch, a feared
    Scottish army battalion, known for their fierce tempers. I’m going to bring that ferocity and culture to my music.“
</p>

<img class="img-fluid" src="/img/MadaldnElleseBBB.jpg" alt="Ellese playing guitar"
    srcset="/img/MadaldnElleseBBB.jpg 600w, /img/MadaldnElleseBBBmedium.jpg 450w, /img/MadaldnElleseBBBsmall.jpg 300w" sizes="75vw">
<img class="img-fluid" src="/img/ArtCouncil-Grant_logo.png"
    alt="Supported using public funding by Arts Council England">]]></content><author><name>Nic The Geek</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bang Bang Bunny are sponsored by The Arts Council England and were awarded the DYCP Grant in 2023 to fuse punk rap with Scottish Gaelic, to popularise an endangered language and history through music. Madaldn, born in Essex, descends from the Elliott Clan. She States “My grandad tells me how his grandad fought in Black Watch, a feared Scottish army battalion, known for their fierce tempers. I’m going to bring that ferocity and culture to my music.“]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Madaldn is also the founder of The Forest Sounds – Music for Everyone</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2023/01/31/FoundingTheForestSounds.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Madaldn is also the founder of The Forest Sounds – Music for Everyone" /><published>2023-01-31T03:45:13+00:00</published><updated>2023-01-31T03:45:13+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2023/01/31/FoundingTheForestSounds</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2023/01/31/FoundingTheForestSounds.html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://theforestsounds.com/">The Forest Sounds – Music for Everyone</a> – an organisation that seeks to
    deliver music production projects across the U.K in order to close the horrendous gender gap in music production.
    Madaldn founded this project when she struggled to work with the multitude of male music producers out there, who
    had their own agendas, and decided to teach herself music production and enable other under represented groups in
    music production to do so too.</p>]]></content><author><name>Nic The Geek</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Forest Sounds – Music for Everyone – an organisation that seeks to deliver music production projects across the U.K in order to close the horrendous gender gap in music production. Madaldn founded this project when she struggled to work with the multitude of male music producers out there, who had their own agendas, and decided to teach herself music production and enable other under represented groups in music production to do so too.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Bang Bang Bunny’s drummer Freddie Rowland</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2023/01/30/BBBdrummerFreddieRowland.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Bang Bang Bunny’s drummer Freddie Rowland" /><published>2023-01-30T03:45:13+00:00</published><updated>2023-01-30T03:45:13+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2023/01/30/BBBdrummerFreddieRowland</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2023/01/30/BBBdrummerFreddieRowland.html"><![CDATA[<p>Bang Bang Bunny’s drummer Freddie Rowland, who is in Love Dogz with Big Brother Winner Pete Bennett and Mad Dog
    Collective says that he is really excited to be in a punk-rap band fronted by an amazing female artist. “I met
    Madaldn in 2022, and I saw something different and worth investing in. Some people might be put off by the fact that
    Madaldn is a single mum of two, but I love a MILF. Jokes aside, it isn’t easy as we all live so far apart and have
    to work within school hours. But we make it happen.”</p>]]></content><author><name>Nic The Geek</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bang Bang Bunny’s drummer Freddie Rowland, who is in Love Dogz with Big Brother Winner Pete Bennett and Mad Dog Collective says that he is really excited to be in a punk-rap band fronted by an amazing female artist. “I met Madaldn in 2022, and I saw something different and worth investing in. Some people might be put off by the fact that Madaldn is a single mum of two, but I love a MILF. Jokes aside, it isn’t easy as we all live so far apart and have to work within school hours. But we make it happen.”]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Bang Bang Bunny are supported by That is Class</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/01/31/BBBThatIsClassSupport.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Bang Bang Bunny are supported by That is Class" /><published>2020-01-31T14:45:13+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-31T14:45:13+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/01/31/BBBThatIsClassSupport</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/01/31/BBBThatIsClassSupport.html"><![CDATA[<p> <a href="https://thatisclass.uk/">That is Class</a> project founder states; “We are looking forward to seeing what
    Bang Bang Bunny is set to deliver. We know they have some great music set to be released and some tricks up their
    sleeve. Bang Bang 2023 is going to be their year and we expect to see them on all the big stages.” </p>]]></content><author><name>Nic The Geek</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[That is Class project founder states; “We are looking forward to seeing what Bang Bang Bunny is set to deliver. We know they have some great music set to be released and some tricks up their sleeve. Bang Bang 2023 is going to be their year and we expect to see them on all the big stages.”]]></summary></entry></feed>